bestparking.com 2015-06-07

# BestParking Mobile

This privacy policy describes how ParkingEdge, LLC ("BestParking.com," “BestParking,” "we," or "us") collects and uses personal information collected via www.BestParking.com and the associated URLs owned or controlled by BestParking.com as well as via mobile applications we make available (collectively, the "Sites"). Please read this privacy policy and the associated Terms of Service before using the Sites or submitting any personal information. To use the Services (as defined in the Terms of Service) you must agree to the Terms of Service and this Privacy Policy (collectively, the “Terms”). Your use of the Services (or any part thereof) constitutes your agreement to the Terms. If you do not agree with the Terms, you may not use the Services. 

The privacy practices set forth in this privacy policy are applicable only to the Sites. If you link to other websites from the Sites, please be aware that BestParking.com does not control the privacy practices of such websites. 

**COLLECTION OF INFORMATION**

BestParking.com may collect personal information, such as names, email and physical addresses, demographic information, and similar information when you submit such information via the Sites. We may also collect information such as your IP address and similar information when you are browsing the Sites. 

**TRACKING TECHNOLOGY**

BestParking.com may use tracking and analytics technology, including cookies, for gathering non-personal information such as browser type and operating system, tracking the number of visitors to the Sites, and understanding how visitors use the Sites. Personal information is not collected via tracking technology; however, if you previously provided personal information, your IP address may be tied to such information (e.g., we may be able to associate an inquiry with a name). We may share aggregate tracking information with third parties and otherwise use such information in any manner. 

**USE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION**

Personal information we collect from you will be used in accordance with the instructions and descriptions specified on our site at the time you submit such information. We may also use such personal information to contact you regarding the Services and to make available offers from third parties that are related to the Services. If you do not wish to receive such third party offers, you may opt out of receiving such offers using the opt-out mechanism we provide in connection with such offers. 

**DISCLOSURE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION**

We may disclose your personal information to our third party business partners who provide parking services and other offers to enable you to take advantage of such services and offers. For example, if you submit the form "Click Here to Request Competitive Bids," we will forward your information to our "Parking Partners" who may opt to offer you parking services. 

We may disclose your personal information to law enforcement officials, regulators, or other third parties in our discretion in connection with any alleged violations of the Terms of Service, violations of law, subpoena, or inquiry by a governmental authority. 

If BestParking.com, or the assets of BestParking.com related to the Services, is acquired by a third party, we will provide your personal information to the party acquiring BestParking.com or such assets and such acquirer will have the right to use such information subject to the terms of this Privacy Policy. 

**DATA SECURITY**

We use reasonable commercial efforts to keep your personal information secure. Only authorized employees, agents and contractors (who have agreed to keep information secure and confidential), and other parties described in this Privacy Policy, have access to this information. 

**PRIVACY CONTACT INFORMATION**

If you have any questions, concerns, or comments about our privacy policy, or if you would like to delete or modify any personal information we may have collected from you, you may contact us at [privacy@bestparking.com](mailto:privacy@bestparking.com). We may modify this Privacy Policy in accordance with the provision of the Terms of Service titled “Changes To The Terms.”
